<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Signal from mars</string>
    <string name="story_from_mars" translatable="false">Signal from mars</string>
    <string name="textview" translatable="false">TextView</string>
    <string name="key_name" translatable="false">name</string>
    <string name="signal_from_mars_title_image" translatable="false">Signal from mars title image</string>
    <string name="enter_your_name">Enter Your Name</string>
    <string name="start_your_adventure">START YOUR ADVENTURE</string>
    <string name="signal_from_mars">Signal from mars</string>

    <string name="page0">On your return trip from studying Saturn\'s rings,you hear a distress
        signal that seems to be coming from surface of Mars.It\'s strange because there hasn\'t
    been a colony there in years.Even stranger it\'s calling you by name: \"Help me, %1$s,you\'re
    my only hope.\"</string>
    <string name="page0choice_1">Stop and investigate</string>
    <string name="page0choice_2">Continue home to Earth</string>

    <string name="page1">You deftly land your ship near where the distress signal generated.You
    didn\'t notice anything strange in your fly-by,but there is a cave in front of you.Behind you
    there is an abandoned rover from early 21st century.</string>
    <string name="page1choice_1">Explore the cave</string>
    <string name="page1choice_2">Explore the rover</string>

    <string name="page2">You continue your course to Earth.Two days later,you receive a transmission
    from HQ saying that they have detected some sort of anomaly on the surface of Mars near an
    abandoned rover. They ask you to investigate but ultimately the choice is yours because your
        mission has already run much longer than planned and supplies are low.</string>
    <string name="page2choice_1">Head back to Mars to investigate</string>
    <string name="page2choice_2">Continue home to earth</string>

    <string name="page3">Your EVa suit is equipped with a headlamp,which you use to navigate the
        cave.After searching for a while your oxygen level is starting to get pretty low.You know
    you should go to refill your tank,but there\'s a very faint light up ahead.</string>
    <string name="page3choice_1">Refill at ship and explore the rover</string>
    <string name="page3choice_2">Continue towards the faint light</string>

    <string name="page4">The rover is covered in dust and most of the solar panels are broken.But
    you are quite surprised to see the on-board system booted up and running.In fact,there is a
    message on the screen;\"%1$s, come to 24.543634,-81.369061.\" Those coordinates aren\'t far but
    you don\'t know if your oxygen will last for a trip there and back.</string>
    <string name="page4choice_1">Explore the coordinates</string>
    <string name="page4choice_2">Return to Earth</string>

    <string name="page5">After a long walk slightly uphill,you end up at the top of a small crater.
    You look around and you are overjoyed to see you favourite android, %1$s-S114.It had been lost
    in a previous mission to Mars! You take it back to the ship and fly back to Earth.</string>

    <string name="page6">You arrive home on Earth. While your mission was a success you forever
    wonder what was sending that signal. Perhaps a future mission will be able to investigate…</string>
</resources>